辛普森一家
第二十四季 第一集
SPS辛普森一家字幕组倾情呈现
字幕仅供学习交流之用 本片版权归FOX所有
麦克贝恩资本认定这是恶意收购
恶搞米蓉泥旗下贝恩资本
恶意收购成其大选绊脚石
在劳动节过后 我不会穿白色套装
翻译: 症 大曦瓜 偏执绝非过错 - -#
校对: 偏执绝非过错 我就是姓刘
后期: 旗木 盖罗  监制: MarcoII
邦妮兔教导: 不要与人分享胡萝卜
Ayn Rand托儿所
欢迎加入 SPS 辛普森一家字幕组 参与翻译后期
详情搜索 Google 或 新浪微博
春田大奖赛
这是Kent Brockman发自首届春田大奖赛的报道
This is Kent Brockman at the 1st Annual Springfield Grand Prix,
一如我镇其他展示活动
which, like all our town showcase events,
本次活动筹备欠周 进展一塌糊涂
is not only poorly planned, it's horribly executed.
缓慢施工中
道路施工        预计封路
Ken Burns: 美国纪录片导演
《帝国大厦的崛起》第一回: 铸造地基
The Making of the Empire State Building Part One: The Basement.
敢不敢有个空子 给个空子
Wait for the gap... Wait for the gap.
Homer 明天也能去买透明胶带啊
Homer, we can buy Scotch tape tomorrow.
有空子了
There's the gap!
空太窄啦
Gap's too small!
自行车队? (法语)
peloton?
如你所见 今天也是 "环春田自行车赛" 最后一个赛段
Apparently, today is also the final stage of the Tour De Springfield bike race.
嘿 那哥们真会骑
Hey, that's some fancy riding.
竞 技 者 舞 会
种族主义者舞会往前走
确凿无疑 两场比赛没有赢家也没有输家
Truthfully, today, there were no losers and no winners
两条终点线横幅都被报废垃圾卷走了
since both finish lines were tangled up in this unholy mess.
里面有人敲东西
I hear tapping from inside.
什么情况啊?
What's goin' on?
好了 大家都来敲动... 你们的脚趾
Well, uh, let's, uh, all start tapping our toes
跟上Scab Calloway和他那个没章法乐队的拍子
to the sounds of Scab Calloway and his non-union band.
你快消停会儿吧
Uh, keep it down in there.
他算你的约会舞伴 还是单纯来充数的?
So, is this a "date" date or just a meaningless friend thing?
- 来充数的 - 真爱约会舞伴
- Meaningless friend thing. - True love super date!
你俩要是来真事儿 整个孩子出来
Well, if you two ever get serious and have a baby,
大概会是这个样子
it'll look something like this.
别听Bart叔叔瞎掰
Don't listen to Uncle Bart.
Lisa和我会倾心抚养你长大的
Lisa and I will raise you in a house of love.
我们才不会有宝宝呢
We're not having a baby.
Jimmy
Jimmy!
老兄 还是跳舞吧
Oh, brother. Let's dance.
看呐
Geek leak!
嘿 Bart 至少还有人约我
Hey, Bart, at least I've got a date.
拜托和我跳舞吧
Dance with me, please.
我得挖苦下她的舞伴
I need to zing my sister.
可以 条件是你明天得交作业
Okay, but you have to do your homework.
逗你玩的
Just kidding.
我早就放弃这回事了
I've given up on that.
赶紧的 像他们那样
Just move your girdle, Yertle.
嘿 你的舞伴
Hey, Lise, your dance partner
刚上了《书呆画报》的封面呢
just made the cover Dorks Illustrated magazine.
我知道你在挖苦我 但至少...
I know that's a zing, but still...
我上了封面呢
the cover!
你给我听清楚了 Bart
Now, you listen to me, Bart.
Milhouse也许不是个理想的约会对象
Milhouse may not be the perfect date.
拜托下句一定要以"但是"开头 拜托
Please let there be a "but" coming, please!
- 但是 - 正中
- But... - Landed it!
至少我有这么个人 他愿意不择手段追我
At least I'm with someone who tries a little too hard
就因为真心喜欢我
because he really likes me.
嘿 不少小妞都很给我Bart面子的噢
Hey, plenty of babes have docked in Porta de Barto.
是啊 不出一个礼拜
Yeah, for about a week.
只要她们看清你这里水有多深
But as soon as they get to know the real you,
保证连头都不给你回
they departo de Barto.
这就是为什么今晚你没有舞伴
That's why you're alone tonight.
天呐 这是真的么?
Oh my God, is that true?
恐怕Lisa是对的 孩子
Yeah, I'm afraid Lisa's right, son.
Nora Ephron: 美国电影导演和编剧
如果已故才女Nora Ephron有教给我们什么...
If the late, great Nora Ephron taught us anything, it's...
糟了 我的充气女朋友也来了
Oh! What's my other inflatable doll doing here?
什么? 咋啦?
What? What?
我一个人在这儿玩呢
I ain't here with no one.
Bart 珍宝
旁人勿近
Bart形状的馄饨
天啊 Lisa说的对
Oh, man, Lisa's right.
没有哪次恋爱长久过
None of these relationships lasted very long.
三天
Three days.
一个课间
One recess.
野外考察中途
Half a field trip.
我在天文馆怎么那么黏人呢?
Why did I have to get so needy at the planetarium?
孩子 有人找我 就说我在泡爆米花儿浴
Boy, if anyone needs me, I'll be taking a popcorn bath.
有次我做梦读《男士健康》杂志 上面这么讲的
It's a thing I read about in a Men's Health magazine in a dream.
老爸 能问你个问题吗?
Dad, can I ask you a question?
你是怎么让妈这样的女人跟你长相厮守的?
How did you ever get a woman like Mom to stay with you?
爹这长相 不找自来啊
Look in the mirror, unplanned miracle.
就这原因吗?
Is that the only reason?
还有就是让生活充满乐趣啊
Well, I also keep things interesting.
够了 谁把微波炉拿走了?
All right, who took the microwave?
看到没?
You see?
嘿 你在看啥?
Hey, what are you looking at?
我的前女友们
My ex-girlfriends.
孩子 我懂你的感受
Aw, boy, I feel for you.
没人喜欢被人拒绝
Nobody likes to be rejected
这痛没法消解 除非到了借酒浇愁的年纪
and it never gets easier, until you can drink.
到时候你就可以酒后痴语 借着电话发泄情绪了
Because then you can express your unfiltered feelings by drunk dialing.
学着点儿
Observe.
嘿 又是我
Hey, it's me again.
他在那儿 是不是?
He's there, isn't he?
我希望这听起来不会太奇怪
Well, I hope this doesn't sound weird,
但我就在你衣柜里
but I'm inside your closet.
这挺给力的 但我还是觉得该去拜访前女友们
Um, that's awesome, but I think I'll visit my ex-girlfriends
证明她们还喜欢着我
and prove they still like me.
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
我挺想你的
I was thinking about you.
离你生日还有三个月还是四个月来着?
It's your birthday in like, three, four months?
我给你开个派对 没问题吧?
Would it be weird if I threw you a party?
Jenny: 因Bart欺骗感情而分手 S20E17
去吃屎吧
Eat my shorts!
Darcy: 因早孕向Bart逼婚 S18E12
死心吧
Drop dead.
Gina Vendetti: Bart在少管所的暴力难友 S15E16
吃我一拳 混蛋
Eat fist, jerk.
Nikki McKenna: 对Bart忽冷忽热让他伤透脑筋 S21E15
你居然还敢出现在我面前...
You've got a lot of nerve showing up here...
却不肯吻我
and not giving me a kiss.
也不看看场合
Inappropriate!
我想你了
I miss you.
色狼
Stalker!
救救我吧
Save me.
Mary Spuckler: Bart为拯救自己养大的小牛被迫和她结婚 S19E17
Mary Spuckler 你是我最后的机会了
Mary Spuckler, you're my last chanc
她在Cletus的女儿里还算标致的
She's pretty cute for Cletus's daughter.
是啊 她小时候喜欢喝牛奶而不是白漆
Yeah, she liked to drink milk as a kid instead of white paint.
你是我孩子吗?
Is you one of my kids?
不是的 先生
No, sir.
证明给我看
Prove it.
A B C...
A, B, C...
行了 行了
All right. All right.
我信你了 小爱因斯坦
You convinced me, Einstein.
你想干嘛?
What you want?
Mary在家吗?
Is Mary here?
恐怕Mary已经离家出走了
I'm afraid Mary done run off.
我们不知道她在哪儿
We knows not where.
真是见鬼了
Dadgummit.
你觉得她还喜欢我吗?
Do you think she still likes me?
嘿 Brandine
Um, hey, Brandine!
Mary还喜欢这个男孩儿吗?
Does Mary still like this boy?
我不知道那个孩子还喜欢什么
I don't know what that girl likes anymore.
自从把她许给井底下的老头 她就离家出走了
She ran away after we engaged her to Old Man Wellbottom.
我会做个好丈夫的
And I was gonna be a good husband, too!
只要让我从井里出来
If'n I ever get out of this well.
得了吧 得了吧
All right. All right now.
是时候省点力气了
That's enough out of you.
但我才...
But I just--
我不敢相信她离家出走了
Oh, I can't believe she ran away.
这东西完全不管用
And this isn't helping.
我得换个更给力的
I better switch to the hard stuff.
好啊 Dubya
Hey, Dubya.
我知道我姐姐去哪儿了
I know where my sister run off to.
纽约
New York City.
纽约?
New York?
《芝麻街》就在那儿 (美国少儿节目)
That's where Sesame Street is.
Oscar: 节目人物之一 喜欢藏在垃圾筒里
你们想过"扔垃圾日"那天Oscar怎么办吗?
Do you ever wonder what happens to Oscar on garbage day?
是的 纽约
Yup, New York.
那个大都市
The big something.
这是她的地址
This here's her address.
祝你好运
Good luck!
我不知道该不该待在这儿 Bart Simpson
I don't know if we should be up here, Bart Simpson.
这话怎么说?
And why is that?
因为地板还没铺好
'Cause the floor ain't finished.
老爹把干草铺上就说整好了
Daddy just covers things with hay and says they're done.
妈 我们能去纽约找这个我认识的女孩吗?
Mom, can we go to New York to find this girl I used to know?
Bart 你真执着
Bart, that's sweet,
但我们得花钱买机票 订旅馆...
but we'd need airplane money, hotel money...
洋基队: 纽约棒球队
还要五百块买洋基队比赛门票 结果还是假票
And $500 for Yankee tickets, which turn out to be bogus.
不买不就好了
Well, don't buy 'em.
但他们对阵的可是紫袜队啊
But they're playing the Purple Sox.
拜托 老爸 你喜欢纽约的
Come on, Dad, you love New York.
而且你最不喜欢的两栋建筑
Now, that your two least favorite buildings
老宾州车站和谢氏球场也都被拆了
have been obliterated: Old Penn Station and Shea Stadium.
讨厌的过时建筑
Lousy, outdated relics!
孩子 还记得上次我们去纽约发生了什么吗?
Boy, do you remember what happene the last time we went to New York?
你再死盯着我妹Marge看
Keep your meat hooks off my sister Marge
别怪我的打手在你太阳穴上开天窗
or my goons will do a soft show on your solar plexus.
你去死吧 J.J 自掘坟墓
You're dead, J.J. Get yourself buried.
嘴巴还挺硬 那好吧 看我怎么收拾你
Tough cookie, huh, well, watch me take a bite out of ya.
我现在准备带枪出去 你刚说谁来着
I'm about to go out shooting and you just said who.
你少给我油嘴滑舌
That's some lip you got on you.
看我把你那张嘴像皮筋一样扯烂 把你打成烙饼
How'd you like me to stretch it like a rubber band and snap you into last week?
你只是故弄玄虚 J.J. 我可是有两把刷子的
You're selling milk, J.J.,and I got a sour stomach.
成功的滋味: 50年代美国电影
Homer 听着怎么像《成功的滋味》的情节
Homer, that sounds like The Sweet Smell of Success.
一点也没成功的感觉
It didn't feel like success.
为什么 小姐们 为什么?
Why, ladies? Why?!
儿子 你可以停止发春了
Son, you can dial down the crazy.
你妈和我商量了一下
Your mother and I talked about it,
我们想到去纽约的办法了
and we found a way to get to New York.
都安排妥了
It's all set, boy.
为了省钱 我们得和别人换房子住
To save money, we're swapping houses.
那些人住在这儿不会糟蹋房子吗?
But don't the people wreck your house when they stay in it?
我又没说换咱家的房子
I didn't say I swapped our house.
你好吗?
Yeah, how ya doing?
我们要在这儿住两个星期
We're staying here for two weeks.
上帝 你是在考验我 是不是?
Lord, you're testing me, aren't you?
继续和你上头的朋友交流吧
Yeah, keep talking to your friend up there.
我们要在你床上滚床单
We'll be doing it on your bed.
还是纽约范儿
New York style.
欢迎来到纽约
推销员
之死
苏斯音乐剧
绝    望
Krusty 出品
恶搞苹果广告语 Think Different
我的平板4
多买 多想
看看这地方
Look at this place.
自打祖先Fievel来过以后
Things have certainly changed
已经发生翻天覆地的变化了
since our ancestor Fievel came here.
Fievel: 电影《美国鼠谭》中的角色
Fievel是部电影里老鼠的名字
Fievel was a mouse in a movie.
是的 但看看现在
Yes, and now look at us.
只有在美国才能这样
Only in America.
中东小吃 S09E01中Homer吃过
肉坨坨 刚出炉的肉坨坨
Khlav Kalash! Get your Khlav Kalash!
拜托 怎么又是那个推小破车的家伙
Oh, geez, not this guy with his stupid little pushcart.
同样出自S9E1 此人卖了Homer不少肉坨坨及佐餐的螃蟹汁
五万平方英尺 全是肉坨坨的地盘
50,000 square feet, huh? All Khlav Kalash!
这儿以前是书店
Used to be bookstore.
没用的书
Books.
快点 该去找Mary了
Come on, let's go find Mary.
游客中心
这是她弟弟给我的地址
This is the address her brother gave me.
在一条街的533号
这 条 街 靠 着 河
不能让老爸带他去 我们去参观名胜吗?
Can't Dad take Bart while we seek out culture?
没问题
You do that.
你知道自己没穿衣服吗?
You know you're missing your clothes?
我还以为我在做梦呢
I thought this was just a dream.
真丢人
Oh, man!
算了 还是换计程车吧
All right, I'll spring for a cab.
感觉好多了
Much better.
到站了
Here we are.
落在车上的东西 甭想再见着了哦
Anything you leave in a cab you'll never see again.
谢天谢地你醒过来了
Oh, uh, oh, thank God you woke up.
我想我的寻爱之旅只剩死路一条了
Oh, I guess my search for true love is doomed.
你学到了人生中意义非凡的一课 孩子
You've learned a very valuable life lesson, boy.
那就是世上没什么真爱
Which is that love doesn't exist,
它只存在于男女婚前的一小段时光里
except briefly between a man and a woman before marriage.
婚后你就只是和某个不怎么喜欢你
After that, it's just hanging out with someone who kind of
但你又没胆量撇下的人过日子了
hates you but you can't get it together to leave.
我去搞点冰淇淋来
I'll get us some ice cream.
这是怎么了 亲爱的?
What's the matter, darling?
谢谢关心 高贵的女士
Thanks for asking, Duchess.
我在这里等一个永远不会出现的女孩
I'm sitting here waiting for a girl that's never gonna show up.
为什么这么肯定?
What makes you so sure?
女孩们不喜欢我
Girls don't like me.
到目前我也没对她们动过真情 但我想我会的
I don't really like them yet either, but I think I'm gonna.
心中的那种感觉在悸动
There's a storm a-brewing down there.
现在就有个女孩站在你面前
Well, there's a girl a-standin' right here.
是我 Mary
It's me, Mary.
哇 你靠什么为生的?
Wow, what are you doing for money?
这份活不是很稳定 而且有些难以启齿
Well, it's not very steady and I'm kind of ashamed.
我是《周六夜现场》的明星演员 (美国综艺节目)
I'm a featured player on Saturday Night Live.
有请Mary Spuckler
Mary Spuckler!
我在扯淡
Aw, I'm lying.
我在这里的生活都很扯淡
My whole life here is a bunch of lies.
我只是个偶尔客串演员的写手罢了
I'm just a writer with a performing option.
咱们还是谈点别的吧
Let's talk about something else.
谈点愉快的
Something nice.
恶搞音乐剧《妈妈咪呀》 剧中歌曲出自阿巴合唱团
爹
地
呀
故事又开始了 因为阿巴合唱团出新歌了
这应该是我们消费得起的地方了
So, this is basically what we can afford.
好的 二号包厢 视野不是很好
Okay, second balcony, partially obstructed view,
没有专用卫生间 还有一点
no bathroom privileges and you must stipulate that,
紧急情况下你们可以换掉聚光灯壳
in emergencies, you can change a spotlight shell.
没事 至少能跟别人说我看过百老汇话剧了
Well, at least I'll be able to say I went to a Broadway show.
你也没资格这么说
You're not allowed to say that.
不看也罢
Oh, forget it.
那么 Bart Simpson
So, Bart Simpson,
你大老远来 就是为了看我一眼?
did you really come all the way here just to see me?
是啊
Yeah.
另外我想或许还能看到
Plus, I thought I might get to see
空调砸到某个倒霉鬼的头上
an air conditioner fall on someone's head.
但我想可能不太现...
But I guess that never really...
- 什么情况?! - 是你老爸吗?
- Ow! What was that?! - Is that your father?
Bart 我希望以后还能找你
Bart, I want to see you again,
但我不想再被大人抓回去了
but I don't want a grownup taking me back.
高线公园: 位于曼哈顿的线型空中花园
明天来高线公园见我
Meet me at the high line tomorrow.
别走漏风声
Keep my secret!
你个臭小...
You little!
我的冰淇淋呢?!
Where's that ice cream?!
真希望别在大屏幕上看到你爸丢人现眼
Just once, I'd like your father
哪怕一次也行
to be on a jumbotron for something good.
我要掐断你该死的凹槽脖子
Damn you and your fluted neck!
话说 你是怎么甩开你老爸的?
So, what did you do with your dad?
没事的 他要上来就得爬楼梯呢
We're safe because you have to climb steps to get up here.
动不了吗?
Can't move?
是啊
No.
我还以为纽约已经没有坏人了呢
I thought there was no crime in New York anymore.
前纽约市长 因打击犯罪获诺贝尔和平奖
该死的朱利安尼
Giuliani!
和我说说春田有什么变化吧
Gimme some news of Springfield.
杂耍Bob: Bart宿敌 几乎每季都会变着花样想整死他
他们又把杂耍Bob放虎归山了
They let Sideshow Bob out of prison again.
这些火车居然还没停运
Huh, didn't know they still ran those trains.
你老妈 还有你老妹呢?
How's your momma and your sister?
正在找廉价的高档文化消费场所呢
Trying to find high culture at low prices.
别过去 Lisa
No, Lisa!
过了这闸机 我们的预算就不够了
If you click that turnstile, it'll blow our budget!
既然他们不在
Well, without them around,
咱们可以牵着手在这里逛上一圈
you and I can walk through the city holding hands,
就像那些大人一样
just like the menfolk do.
我可以在你的鼻音里沉醉一整天
I could listen to your twang all day.
愿意听我给你唱首歌吗?
Would you care to hear it in song?
因为我写了首哦 为了你
'Cause I wrote one 'bout you.
我能在中间来段说唱吗?
Can I do a rap in the middle of it?
静静听就行了
Or you could just listen.
先生 能借你的吉他用用吗?
Sir, may I borrow your guitar?
当然 没问题 真正赚钱的是这个提箱
Sure, sure. It's the case that makes money.
♪ 那梦中的男孩回到我身边♪
♪ A boy I knew turned up again ♪
♪ 还记得那时追着他♪
♪ Kind of liked him way back when ♪
♪ 在牲口栏后跑的那天♪
♪ Chased him round the livestock bend... ♪
踏着我的滑板
Rolling on my skateboard,
像毒贩样摇摆
pimping like a drug lord...
♪ 即将迈入我的成年♪
♪ Well I'm on the cusp of womanhood ♪
♪ 而我喜欢那个♪
♪ And I like a boy ♪
♪ 没有什么本事♪
♪ That ain't no good at nothin' ♪
♪ 却让我开怀的男孩♪
♪ 'Cept making me smile ♪
♪ 就是Bart♪
♪ That's Bart. ♪
♪ 我想起了以前的时光♪
♪ I thought my old ways I had shed ♪
♪ 但唯独记得他的小刺头♪
♪ But I sure missed his cylinder head ♪
♪ 现在他又回来了 噢 对♪
♪ Now that boy has a-come to me, oh, yes ♪
♪ B-A-R 那T在哪里?♪
♪ B-A-R, now where's that T? ♪
♪ 在哪里? 不知道♪
♪ Where is it? I don't know ♪
♪ 那就是 Bart♪
♪ Oh, that's Bart. ♪
我真的喜欢你 Bart Simpson
I really like you, Bart Simpson.
我是来带你回去的 Mary
I've come to take you back, Mary.
老爹?
Daddy?
抱歉 亲爱的 你老娘想你 但她就是说不出口
Sorry, honey, your mother misses you but she just can't say it.
因为驴子踢坏了她的下巴
That's 'cause the donkey busted her jaw.
她会没事的
She'll be fine.
还是你娘
Your mother too.
游遍纽约
曼哈顿蛤蜊汤
能来点新鲜的么?
好吧 百老汇太贵
All right, Broadway's too expensive,
博物馆人满为患
the museums are over-curated,
但今晚公园里有莎士比亚的戏
But Shakespeare in the Park is tonight
而且不收门票
and the tickets are free.
戴拉寇特剧院
莎翁话剧
在此排队
详参《哈姆雷特》
快来买啊 绿帽角 褶领边和Yorik的头骨
Get your cuckold's horns, neck ruffles, Yorik skulls!
给我来顶绿帽角
I'll take a cuckold's horn!
还真管用
It works!
女士们先生们 我有一个通知要传达
Ladies and gentlemen, I have an announcement.
女 士 们 先 生 们 我 有 一 个 通 知 要 传 达
Lad-ies and gen-tle-men, I have an an-nounce-ment--
这不是五音韵啊
That's not iambic pentameter!
今天晚上的节目恐怕要取消了
I'm afraid that tonight's show has been cancelled.
- 为什么? - 怎么会这样?
- Why? - Wherefore?
扮演Monague家庭的Baldwin兄弟
The Baldwin brothers, who were, uh, playing the Monague family
以及扮演Capulet家庭的Sheen/Estevez组合
and the Sheen/Estevez clan, our Capulets,
退出了节目的制作
have quit the production.
你们表演得糟透了 还把土豆沙拉全都吃光了
You guys suck at acting and you ate all the potato salad.
你们的表演才逊毙了 而且按理应该先到先吃
No, you suck at acting and it's first come, first serve!
那些土豆沙拉是我做的
I made that potato salad!
一帮低能 包装上明明写着Zaybar's
Well, uh, idiot, it says Zaybar's on the package!
那是因为他在Zaybar's上班
He works at Zaybar's.
我们都在Zaybar's上班
We all work at Zaybar's.
十分抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你们是来看罗密欧与朱丽叶的 不是家庭矛盾
You came to see Romeo and Juliet, not feuding families.
出场的观众请在左边排队缓慢离场
Uh, the long, slow line to leave the theatre forms on the left.
我们要经过那个鼓乐圈
Aw, and we have to walk by a drum circle!
再快点 再恼人点
Faster, man! More annoying!
先不要走
Not so fast!
我们是来看莎士比亚的 我们就一定要看到
We came for Shakespeare and we're gonna see Shakespeare.
想来演一出的人
Anyone who wants to be in this,
找件紧身衣 到后台来会合
grab a doublet and meet me backstage!
姑娘 不知可否容我参与?
Is there, mayhaps, a bit of business for me?
我本只想邀请业余爱好者的
I was thinking amateurs only.
Taco是一种墨西哥传统食物
鄙人仅出演过Taco Bueno广告里那穷凶极恶的热狗
Well, my only professional job was playing
a nefarious hot dog in an ad for Taco Bueno.
你这新鲜的玉米卷
You fresh-made tacos will never
永远比不上煮熟的热狗
defeat pre-boiled hot dogs!
求你了 我还欠耶鲁戏剧学院二十万美金呢
Please, I owe Yale Drama School $200,000.
他们不停打电话骚扰我妈
They keep calling my mother.
好吧 你来吧
Fine! You're in.
事先提个醒 我非常怯场
I must warn you, I have crippling stage fright.
天 真是恼人
Oh, for the love of God!
因为再也没有一个故事
For never was a story of more woe
悲惨于罗密欧和朱丽叶的情史
than this of Juliet and her Romeo.
探寻文化之旅 行将终结
Our search for culture is thus concluded,
人们兜中手机 静音和谐
For the Bard of Avon is well suited
都被静音 人们的手机
to a crowd with every cell phone muted.
我都不会说话了
Geez, I can't stop talking like this.
让我们继续
Hey, don't ever stop!
今晚在纽约 我们成功了
Because, tonight, we made it in New York.
就是这帮人占领了剧场?
Those the people who took over the theatre?
上胡椒喷雾和水枪 尝尝纽约热情的熊抱和激吻吧
Pepper spray and power wash--the New York hug and kiss.
24小时自助仓库
正式名: NBC电视网
Mary 你听我说
Now, Mary, you listen to me.
我算是你三分之一个的父亲 你必须和我回去
I'm one-third your father and you're gonna come back.
我先失陪一下
If y'all will excuse me,
我要在回家之前梳洗一下
I gotta freshen up for the ride home.
好好享受你最后的室内豪华厕所吧
Enjoy your fancy-schmancy in-house for the last time.
我去去就来
Um, I've got to go.
去哪?
Go where?
既然都来这了
Uh, well, since we're here,
Al Roker: 著名天气预报主持人
我想去要Al Roker的签名
I'm gonna go try to get Al Roker's autograph.
给你 小粉丝
Here you go, little fan.
马上会有暴风雨哟
Killer storm on the way.
我要去把这个签名卖掉
Um, I gonna go try to sell this.
那我把它买回来吧
I'll buy it back.
再见了 Bart 别担心
Goodbye, Bart, and don't worry,
还会有其他人来和你好的
there'll be other Mary Spucklers,
比如我的姐妹"Mary Zeke"或者"Mary不太对"
including my sisters Mary Zeke and Mary Not Quite Right.
Bart 如果有女孩想改变你 一定要听她
Bart, if any girl tries to fix you, let 'em,
因为你确实有些坏毛病
because you got a couple of big problems.
不过总的说 你很棒
But mostly, you're great!
小子 告诉我Mary去哪了
Boy, you tell me where Mary's gone!
我不能说
I can't.
小子 在这乡巴佬面前你最好坦白从宽
Boy, you squeal like a piggy for the hillbilly man.
我不能说 Mary让我知道女孩还是有可能喜欢我的
I can't because Mary's the girl that proves that girls can like me.
如果我告密 她就不会再喜欢我了
And she wouldn't like me anymore if I gave her up.
所以我不会说 就算你像糟蹋英语一样折磨我
So I won't, even if you torture me like you do the English language.
你这你这你这熊孩子
Well, if that ain't aren't the isn't.
看来只能等Mary自己回家了
I guess I just gotta let Mary find her own way.
走 我们快回春田吧
Come on, let's head on back to Springfield.
给我一张哐叽哐叽的站票 谢谢
Uh, one on-getter for the clickity clack, please.
你很想她吧 是吧 孩子?
You miss her, don't you, son?
想要一张她的照片放在钱包里吗?
You want a picture of her for your wallet?
她大概在B-3区
Oh, she's somewhere in B-3.
谢谢
Thanks, man.
快看这小子
Aw, look at that.
我儿子终于明白
My little guy's finally realizing
大人的心理有多复杂了
how complicated grownup feelings can be.
最起码比罗密欧朱丽叶强吧
Well, at least it didn't end as bad as Romeo and Juliet.
这倒是
No kidding.
我看到你们的报道了
I saw your reviews.
吟游诗人的逝去
我特意强调不能乱加批评
I specifically said, no critics!
真是气死人了
This is outrageous!
不过是好评诶
Ooh, but they like me.
希望你们喜欢今天这一集
I hope you enjoyed the show tonight.
如果担心我是不是被空调砸出毛病了
And if you're worried about when the air conditioner
请放心 那是我们的特技替身演员
fell on my head, rest assured it was a stunt man,
我们会负责照顾他全家的
and his family is being well taken care of.
在此我们欢迎大家提供沙发片头的点子
But we're here to ask if you have an idea for a couch gag.
我们会采纳最棒的点子做成动画哦
The best submission will be animated and appear on the show.
可不可以偷上传人的信用卡?
Do we screw them on the credit?
当然不 详情请登陆辛普森一家官网
No! For details, log on to TheSimpsons.com.
我正在上传我的
I'm submitting mine now.
把五口人脑袋都换成Bart的
欢迎加入 SPS 辛普森一家字幕组 参与翻译后期
详情搜索 Google 或 新浪微博